const data = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "What is the name of the main protagonist in the Halo series?",
        answer: "Master Chief."
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which video game franchise features the character Trevor Phillips?",
        answer: "Grand Theft Auto (GTA)."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "In which game do players fight against the Locust Horde?",
        answer: "Gears of War."
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the main objective in Minecraft?",
        answer: "To survive and build in a blocky, procedurally generated world."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which game features the iconic character Lara Croft?",
        answer: "Tomb Raider."
    },
    // {
    //     id: 5,
    //     question: "What is the name of the city in which the game Cyberpunk 2077 is set?",
    //     answer: "Night City."
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 6,
    //     question: "In which game do players control a character named Link?",
    //     answer: "The Legend of Zelda."
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 7,
    //     question: "What is the main goal in the game 'Among Us'?",
    //     answer: "To complete tasks and identify impostors."
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 8,
    //     question: "Which game series is known for its 'Animus' machine and historical settings?",
    //     answer: "Assassin's Creed."
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 9,
    //     question: "What is the name of the post-apocalyptic world in Fallout?",
    //     answer: "The Wasteland."
    // }
];

export default data